{
    "id": "0b7e8b95fcee47ce92be510a423bbb47",
    "title": "Sentence Completion",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "After the visitors ……………. I went into my room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone",
                "had gone",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9b08b849c3847cfb72c54a7c48bca14"
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused ………………….. by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "interrogated",
                "were interrogating",
                "being interrogated",
                "were being interrogated"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "9579ddab904c402bb88679f02d5d8077"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one ……………….. a fraudster.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "likes",
                "is liking",
                "liked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56159e23acc64251b4c035f63a99a3f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… our country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall not betray",
                "shall not betrayed",
                "do not shall betray"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e3067916e56d4bcdb1134b030b8be9bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. your letter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "was received",
                "had received",
                "would receive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d63800fd1612470c9fdda4d1173ce1c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It takes two ——— a quarrel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to making",
                "to make",
                "to made",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b177d8b22fd40039cff2363b7ec63f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ………………… red-handed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "was caught",
                "has caught",
                "would catch"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c6061c2284c4d7ab61c300bb09a4abe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Delhi-Mumbai flight ……………….. by two hours due to a bomb scare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delayed",
                "has delayed",
                "was delayed",
                "had delayed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7c155c5c0a6944fc82addf39cdb190a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The stadium …………………. with dance and music as artists from various parts of the world ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reverberate, performed",
                "reverberated, performed",
                "was reverberated, performed",
                "reverberated, was performed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a205269ec74841f6aad56649d63f7146"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. animals, but he also ……………….. many man eaters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "love, kill",
                "loved, killed",
                "was loved, was killed",
                "had loved, had killed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0ee3cca139042a69a2951566c6d0ed1"
        }
    ]
}